Previously on Reacher...
《烈探雷彻》前情提要
He said 650 at 100K each.
他说:“六千五 每手十万”
It could be a transfer of 65 million, a $65 million cover-up,
可能是六千五百万的转账 六千五百万的掩饰费
a $65 million bribe.
六千五百万的贿赂款
We got a suspect.
我们找到了一个嫌疑人
Azhari Mahmoud.
阿扎里马哈茂德
He's known to Interpol as a weapons broker for terrorist organizations.
国际刑警组织 知道他是恐怖组织的武器经纪人
He's a ghost. No pictures of him anywhere.
“他如幽灵一般 任何地方都没有他的照片”
If these are supposed to be fractions, then it's sloppy work.
如果这些是分数 那写下这些数字的人就太粗心了
On each sheet there's 26 or 27 numerical tabulations.
每张纸上有26或27个数字列表
So, the real question is what kind of somethings were they counting?
真正的问题是 他们在算什么事的时间
You don't have to be lonely tonight.
今晚你不必孤单
There were hit men who tried to kill us in Atlantic City.
在大西洋城的时候 有杀手曾经想杀了我们
They failed, but they had a parking pass for a company called New Age.
他们失败了 但他们有一张 叫新时代的公司的停车证
New Age is an aerospace company.
新时代是一家航空航天公司
I'm Marlo Burns, New Age Director of Operations.
我是马洛伯恩斯 新时代的运营总监
The parking pass was issued to a man named Trevor Saropian.
停车证被发给了 一个叫特雷弗萨罗皮安的男人
- Where's his car? - We decided to take it with us.
- 他的车在哪儿  - 我们决定把车带走
Holy shit. It's Swan.
天啊 是斯旺
He was working at New Age
他曾在新世纪工作
with the people who've been trying to kill us.
跟一直想杀了我们的这群人一起
Great. Well, we drove a car through a window
真棒 我们开车撞破窗户
so that I could read workers comp pleadings
这样我就可以阅读 一位五年前在新时代
for a secretary who slipped on New Age stairs five years ago.
滑倒的秘书的工伤赔偿诉状了
So glad we risked prison for that.
真开心我们为此冒着坐牢的风险
Yeah, I got nothing, too. No new information.
是啊 我也一无所获 没有新线索
Well, I wouldn't say we haven't found any new information.
我倒是觉得我们发现了一些新线索
I mean, we've got three special investigators dead,
我们有三名特别调查员死亡
one in the wind,
一名在逃
and the one who's missing just happens to be the one who worked for New Age.
而失踪的那位刚好在新时代工作过
What? Look, someone's got to say it.
怎么了 总得有人说出来
Was Swan working with these guys or with these guys?
斯旺是这些人的同事还是同谋
Swan's not dirty.
斯旺是良民
- Look, man, we all want to believe that he isn't... - I know Swan. We all do.
- 我们都想相信他没... - 我了解斯旺 我们都了解
And you don't think there's even a chance...
你觉得那一点可能性都没有吗
No. I don't.
绝不可能
Focus on what we found.
专注于我们的发现
Brad?
“布拉德”
Stacy?
史黛西
This is a brad.
我说的是这种“布拉德”
That is a fastener. Two names for something that size is stupid.
那是紧固件 这么小的东西 居然有两个名字 太蠢了
So is this conversation.
这段对话也很蠢
Well, speaking of names,
说起名字
just found our man in the employee directory.
我刚在员工目录中 发现了我们的人的名字
Seems Swan's title was assistant director of security.
看来斯旺的职位是安全总监助理
Shane Langston, director of security.
“谢恩兰斯顿 安全总监”
Maybe he's the guy I got on the phone in Atlantic City.
也许在大西洋城 跟我通话的就是这个人
Why would you say that?
何出此言
He's the security boss and bosses give orders
他是安全部门的老大 负责发号施令
and the guys we killed had orders to take us out.
我们杀掉的那些人 接到命令要干掉我们
Just a theory. He could be the guy that got Swan caught up in all this.
这只是推测 他可能是 让斯旺陷入这一切的罪魁祸首
Well, if Swan didn't pull him into it first...
如果不是斯旺先让他卷进去的话
I already told you... Aren't you the guy that said that assumptions kill?
- 我已经跟你说了... - 你不是说假设害死人吗
Well, you're assuming that Swan's the same guy he was back in the 110.
你在假设斯旺 离开110小组后没有变化
Hey, this is the guy Reacher chased down outside of Saropian's house.
嘿 这就是雷彻 在萨罗皮安家外面追的那个人
Same photo as his ID badge.
跟他身份证的照片一致
Associate security officer.
副安全官员
Well, that's great.
真不错
Swan, Collins,
斯旺 柯林斯
that's two New Age security personnel somehow involved in this.
两名新时代的安全部门人员与此有关
Now we got to look into all these fuckers. Don't forget Marlo Burns.
- 现在我们得调查所有这些混蛋 - 别忘了马洛伯恩斯
She knew she was sending us right into a buzzsaw when she gave us Saropian's address.
是她置我们于险境 她给了我们萨罗皮安的地址
So, the entire company's suspect.
所以整个公司都很可疑
We got over a thousand employees. How we gonna tackle that?
这个公司有一千多名员工 我们怎么查这么多人
One at a time.
一次一个
Last night you asked for a late night warrant for some defense firm,
昨晚 你申请了 某国防公司的深夜搜查令
and an hour later, the place is hit with a smash-and-grab.
而一个小时后 这地方就发生了入室盗窃
Okay, do you know how that makes this department look?
你知道这让我们看起来像什么吗
Like we're five steps behind everything.
就好像我们步步落后一样
I made those applications when I had enough for a warrant.
我收集到了足够多的证据 才申请的搜查令
And while you were waiting for them, all the evidence that you would have collected
而在你等待搜查令的时候 你本该从那里收集的证据
from that place is all cleaned out.
已经全部被带走了
And I'll bet you that it is those tin soldiers
我跟你打赌 就是那些
that you were supposed to be keeping your black eye on.
给你打出黑眼圈的破军人干的
It wasn't the army brats. I made it crystal clear to them
不是那群军队混混干的 我跟他们说得很清楚
not to color outside the lines. Oh, I see.
- 让他们守规矩  - 我知道了
You thought, if you told them nicely, they'd play along?
你觉得你好好跟他们说话 他们就会配合
You're NYPD.
你是纽约市警察局的
These are fucking PIs, for Chrissakes.
天啊 这些人都是他妈的私家侦探
Is this too fucking much for you, Russo?
这超出你的能力范围了吗 拉索
Lieutenant, lower your voice.
中尉 小声点
Lower my voice?
小声点
You're telling me to lower my voice in my own fucking office?
你让我在我自己的办公室里 讲话小声点
Okay.
好吧
Would you please go and find out what they learned, all right?
请你去了解一下 他们都发现了什么 好吗
Am I asking you nicely enough, Russo?
我这么说话够客气了吧 拉索
I'll get it handled. Great.
- 我会处理好的 - 很好
Close the door.
关门
Who put this song on?
谁放的这首歌
This is the Talking Heads.
这是传声头像乐队的歌
You got beef with the Talking Heads? We're in New York.
你跟传声头像乐队有仇吗  我们现在在纽约呢
They're a New York band.
他们是纽约的乐队
They're a Rhode Island band that moved to New York
搬到了纽约的罗德岛乐队
and no, I don't have a beef with them. It's just...
没 我跟他们没仇 只是
"Road to Nowhere," when we're sitting here getting nowhere,
《此路不通》  刚好我们坐在这儿毫无进展
seems a little defeatist.
貌似有点晦气
Besides, it's not even their best song.
而且这不是他们最好的歌
Probably prefer "Psycho Killer."
我更喜欢《变态杀手》
Um, I might have something.
我可能找到线索了
I've been scrubbing the drives for everything Swan-related.
我一直在找U盘里 所有和斯旺有关的内容
- And? - And I found an anomaly.
- 然后呢  - 我发现了一件反常的事
He's the assistant director of security,
他是安全总监助理
so all of his emails have Langston-- his boss--
他所有的电子邮件 都抄送了他的上司兰斯顿
and a half-dozen other security personnel cc'd on them.
以及其他六名安保人员
Makes sense. I mean, they're a team. They share information.
合情合理 他们是一个团队 得共享信息
But he didn't share everything.
但他没有分享一切
There are multiple emails between Swan and our old friend Marlo Burns.
有几封邮件是斯旺 和我们的老朋友马洛伯恩斯的
Just them. No one else copied.
只有他们俩 没有抄送其他人
About what?
是关于什么的
Music, but not really.
音乐 但又不全是
How do you know?
你怎么知道
He wrote,
他写道
"I was listening to an album the other day,
“前几天我在听一张专辑
thought you might like it. Jimi Hendrix, Bold as Love.
“我觉得你可能会喜欢 吉米亨德里克斯的《大胆如爱》
The sixth song is amazing. Take a listen, tell me what you think."
“第六首歌太赞了 听听看 告诉我你的想法”
Swan hated Hendrix. Anything with hard guitar.
斯旺很讨厌亨德里克斯 他讨厌任何吵闹的吉他曲...
No Skynyrd, no Hendrix, no Zeppelin, no Who.
不弹斯金纳德 齐柏林 亨德里克斯和谁人乐队的歌
I mean, that was his rule. He's leaving everyone else off the email
- 这是他的原则 - 他没有让其他人看这封邮件
and saying he loved something we know he hated.
而他在邮件里说他喜欢 我们知道他讨厌的东西
Could be code.
可能是暗号
Or it could be a guy trying to get laid.
或者也可能是春心萌动
I mean, I once told a girl I loved Georgia O'Keeffe.
我曾经跟一个女孩说 我喜欢乔治亚欧姬芙
We say things.
我们会说这种话
Yeah. It says the sixth track is called "Little Wing."
是的 我查到第六首歌叫《小翅膀》
Hold on.
等等
I ever tell you you're smart, Neagley? Not nearly enough.
- 我说过你很聪明吗 内格利  - 还远远不够
Right here. A file on a federal defense project called Little Wing,
这里 这是一份联邦国防项目的文件 项目名叫“小翅膀”
by far the biggest contract New Age has ever had.
这是迄今为止 新时代签下的最大的合同
Four times the size of anything I've seen anywhere else in their records.
是我在其他记录中见过的四倍
A nine-figure contract.
一份九位数的合同
People have murdered for less.
人们为了更少的利益杀人
Look at this interoffice memo.
看看这份办公室内部备忘录
Seems a test for the Little Wing tech was held for some military brass,
他们似乎为一些军事要员 甚至包括一位参议员
even a senator.
对小翅膀科技进行了测试
But what kind of test? And where?
什么测试 在哪儿测的
Doesn't say,
上面没写
but they do note that Senator Malcolm Lavoy
但他们确实指出 参议员马尔科姆拉沃伊
assured he would do all he could to get the congressional votes to make Little Wing a reality.
保证他会获得国会的选票 让小翅膀变成现实
And I quote,
我引用原文
"He fully believes in the work we're doing here at New Age
“他完全相信我们 在新时代做的这项工作
and will do whatever it takes to help us."
“并且会不惜一切代价帮助我们”
Lavoy would fully believe in Snuffleupagus you pay him enough.
如果你给的钱够多 拉沃伊连《芝麻街》的史纳菲都信
You know this guy?
你知道这个人
By reputation. In D.C., Lavoy's what's known as a paper bag.
有所耳闻 在华盛顿特区 拉沃伊被称为“纸袋”
His politics and his vote go whichever way the wind's blowing.
他的政治方针和投票都飘忽不定
He's known to do some shady shit.
众所周知 他会做见不得人的事
So, if New Age stands to make a fortune on
所以如果新时代能靠政府合同发财
a government contract and Lavoy is his champion in Congress,
而拉沃伊是他们在国会的拥护者
it stands to reason New Age is the wind blowing Lavoy's bag.
这就说明新时代 让拉沃伊的口袋装得满满的
That sounds wrong.
这听起来不对
So, Swan, who's missing, maybe dirty, maybe not,
所以 失踪且尚不清楚 是否是良民的斯旺
is code-texting Marlo Burns, who tried to have us killed
给之前想杀了我们的马洛伯恩斯
about a program supported
发了含有代码的邮件
by an ethically-compromised politician.
其内容是关于 一个道德败坏的政客支持的项目
We need talk to Malcolm Lavoy.
我们得跟马尔科姆拉沃伊谈谈
We'll never get close enough to a senator to find out what he may or may not know.
我们永远没法接近参议员 从他口中套话
Oh, we don't need to. Those guys never even know what they're voting for.
我们不需要接近他 这些人 从来都不清楚自己在给什么投票
Thousand-page bills, the legislative record, they don't read that stuff.
一千页的法案 立法记录 他们不会读那些东西的
They just vote the way they're told to. But his legislative director--
他们只会按照被告知的方式投票 但他的立法主任
they're the guys who actually craft and draft the laws,
实际上是他们制定并起草法案
which is good for us because those guys have no security detail.
这对我们有利 因为这些人没有安保人员
Okay, but why would those people talk to us?
这些人为什么要跟我们说呢
I can make it so they'll be begging to tell us what they know.
我可以让他们说话 让他们求着告诉我们他们知道的事
Something you want to share with the class?
你有什么想跟我们分享的事情吗
Look, there's a lot of powerful people in D.C. with, uh...
听着 华盛顿特区有很多有权势的人
confidential problems.
都有见不得光的事
Mainly unsavory, but legal, things they do
主要是不大光彩 但是合法的
in private that they'd rather not get made public.
是一些他们不愿公开的私人行为
My job is to make sure that their personal business stays personal.
我的工作就是 确保他们的私事永不见光
And the people who know secrets, they keep those secrets.
而知道秘密的人会保守住这些秘密
So, you blackmail?
所以 你敲诈勒索
I incentivize.
我是激励他们
Sounds sleazy, O'D.
听起来很不道德 奥唐纳
It's sleazy-adjacent.
比不道德差那么一点
Hey, I got private school tuition to pay for, okay?
嘿 我得付私立学校的学费 好吗
I never break the law.
我从不违法
I simply present the facts to people and let them know
我只是把事实摆在人们面前 让他们知道
which way the river's gonna flow if they choose the wrong course of action.
如果他们做错了选择会发生什么
You give me ten minutes to make some phone calls,
给我十分钟打几个电话
I'll get the name of the legislative director and an Achilles' heel.
我会找到立法主任的名字 和他的致命弱点
Do it.
动手吧
All right.
好的
Thank you.
谢谢
Reacher, I know you don't want to talk about Swan...
我知道你不想说斯旺...
Swan's clean. If he wasn't, he wouldn't have disappeared like the rest of the guys.
斯旺是清白的 如果他有问题 他不会像其他人一样消失
But he didn't disappear like the rest of the guys.
但他并没有像其他人一样消失
His body was never found His place wasn't trashed.
他的尸体始终没被发现 他的家也没被毁
He wouldn't just leave his dog to die. Not who Swan was.
他不会就这么让他的狗渴死 斯旺不是那种人
Maybe.
也许吧
Or maybe he ran off so fast
也许他迅速逃跑
because he knew three pissed-off soldiers and a kaiju were coming for him.
因为他知道三个愤怒的士兵 和一头怪兽会去找他
Dog was collateral damage.
狗受到了附带伤害
Okay, look, we don't know what Swan's been up to since the 110th ended. Right?
好吧 听我说 我们不知道 110小组解散后 斯旺在忙什么
I mean, he could have money problems. He could have been taking payoffs.
他可能缺钱 可能收脏钱
Would you believe it if somebody told you I was taking payoffs?
如果有人告诉你我收脏钱 你会相信吗
No.
不会
I'm just saying
我只是说
maybe we don't know some people as well as we think we do.
也许我们不像 我们想象中那么了解某些人
There's no way the Tony Swan I recruited is a part of this.
我招募的托尼斯旺 绝对不可能参与此事
End of story.
不说了
See the look on their faces when we whipped out our badges?
你看到我们拿出军徽时 他们脸上的表情了吗
They looked like Ralph Terry
他们看起来像比尔马泽罗斯基
when Bill Mazeroski hit his game seven walk-off homer on him.
在第七场比赛中 打出本垒打时的拉夫尔特里
Mazeroski? New rule, kid,
马泽罗斯基 新规矩 孩子
you can't reference
你不能引用
shit from more than a decade before you were born.
你出生十多年前的人的例子
Go, Bucs.
滚开 海盗
We're so close to wrapping up this case I can taste it.
我们就快结案了
What do you think they're gonna give us-- Commendations, promotions?
你觉得他们会给我们什么  表扬 升职
I like the sound of that.
听起来还不错
Pump the brakes, Major.
就此打住 少校
There's still a hell of a lot of work ahead.
还有一大堆工作要做呢
More arrests to be made. Infrastructure to dismantle.
还要逮捕更多人 要拆除基础设施
Whole networks of cargo planes, jeeps and helicopters across three continents.
调查跨越三大洲的 货机 吉普车 直升机网络
Just take the W, Gramps.
老爷爷 庆祝胜利吧
Don't sass your elders.
不要辱骂长辈
Yeah. Take it easy on him, guys. He hasn't had his nap yet.
就是 对他好点 他都不打瞌睡的
Damn. Looks like we got some Ivory Soap over here, Reacher.
好家伙 看来我们这里有象牙皂啊 雷彻
Meaning?
什么意思
Meaning this shit's so pure it floats.
意思是 这玩意很纯 会漂起来
How pure?
有多纯
Ninety-nine percent.
百分之九十九
No wonder kids are getting hooked on this shit left and right.
难怪到处都是迷上这玩意的孩子
At ease, sports fans, don't get up.
放松 体育迷们 不用站起来
I hear congratulations are in order.
我听说就快结案了
That's quite the buy 'n bust.
卧底买卖收获颇丰啊
Kilos of poison
几公斤的毒品
and a handful of scumbag dealers off the streets
还有几个被逮捕的毒贩
and ratting on their friends for us.
向我们出卖他们的朋友
These are the small fish. We'll catch the sharks soon enough.
这些都是小鱼 我们很快就会钓到大鱼的
What did I tell you when you started this thing?
你开始查这事的时候 我怎么跟你说的
This case is gonna be a monster. Unleash the hounds.
“这个案子会是个怪物 所以关门放狗”
Seems you did.
看来你做到了
Speaking of monsters,
说到怪物
how's Hortense the Fourth?
霍滕斯四世怎么样了
20 months, already into his terrible twos.
二十个月前 已经进入可怕的两岁期了
Apparently, he's a prodigy.
显然 他是个神童
Good work, everyone. Good work.
各位 干得好
Talking about a prodigy,
说起神童
you're about to hit your Bacardi milestone.
你就要达到百加得151里程碑了
151 cases closed.
已经侦破151起案件了
Don't add it to the stats sheets till it's done.
在案子完成前 不要加到统计表里
People in our profession re sent overseas
我们这一行的人会被派往海外
awhere we're shot at, bombed, blasted from IEDs.
在那里 我们会被枪击 被轰炸 被简易爆炸装置炸飞
Then these assholes make more money selling
然后这些混蛋会靠卖这玩意
this shit than all our pensions combined.
赚的比我们所有人的养老金总和都多
It's fucked up.
真不公平
All I'm saying.
我就说说而已
How much is 48 bricks worth, anyway?
对了 48公斤值多少钱
one's missing. There's 47, not 48.
少了一公斤 是47公斤 不是48公斤
In an investigation, details matter.
在调查中 细节很重要
Brick of heroin's a hell of a detail.
海洛因的数量是个细节
That's impossible. I counted 48 at point of sale.
那不可能 我在销售点数过 是48公斤
Either you miscounted or they palmed one back to short you.
要么是你数错了 要么就是有人递错了
No, no, no. You do shit like that, you're not in the game for long.
不会 只有新手才会犯这种错误
I know we loaded 48 bricks into Swan's ride.
我知道我们 往斯旺的车里装了48公斤
Let's check your car.
我们查查你的车
Nothing.
什么都没有
Mystery solved.
谜团解开了
Must have fallen back there when I was driving and gotten stuck.
肯定是我开车的时候掉到后面卡住了
Guess the first round's on me tonight for that fuckup.
因为这个失误 我猜今晚第一轮该我请客
Losing a key of H, I'd say that's worth two rounds.
掉了一公斤的海洛因 我得说应该请两轮
What?
什么
Nothing.
没什么
I'd actually forgotten about that, but it doesn't support your argument.
其实我都忘记这件事了 但这不支持你的论点
Swan could have been stealing drugs and just panicked and gave them back.
斯旺可能本来偷了毒品 而他只是惊慌失措 并将其归还
Maybe he regretted letting a chance at big money go by.
也许他后悔错过了这个赚大钱的机会
Maybe something like Little Wing came along
也许小翅膀项目来了
and he couldn't pass up that kind of opportunity again.
他不能再次错过赚钱的机会
That's a lot of maybes. My gut tells me he's a good man.
有很多种可能 我的直觉告诉我他是个好人
Your gut's never been wrong before?
你的直觉以前从没出过错吗
You know what I think?
你知道我是怎么想的吗
You want Swan to be innocent because you hired him into the 110th,
你希望斯旺是无辜的 因为是你招募他到110小组的
and if he's involved in something like this,
如果他参与此事 你会做一些蠢事
you'd do something stupid like blame yourself for our friends' deaths.
比如你会因为我们朋友的死而自责
Which, like I said, would be stupid.
而正如我所说 这样很蠢
Let's just see what O'Donnell found.
我们看看奥唐纳发现了什么
- Mr. Mason? - Dr. Elzogby.
梅森先生 我是埃尔佐格比医生
So, I read your intake, and upon first glance, I got to say,
我看了你的病历 乍一看 我不得不说
got a few questions.
有几个问题
Look, I like a payday as much as the next guy, but you're quite a handsome fella.
我和所有人一样都喜欢钱 但你是个英俊的小伙子
Now, I'm not here to tell you how to live your life, but
我不会告诉你该怎么过你的生活
are you really certain you want me to give you a new face?
但你真的想让我给你整个新面孔吗
In a manner of speaking.
从某种意义上来说
Don't struggle.
别挣扎
You're a doctor, you know what's happening.
你是医生 你知道发生了什么
Your trachea is severed.
你的气管被割破了
Blood is entering your lungs, you're drowning,
血液正在肺部 你快憋死了
your brain is deprived of oxygen and your nervous system's shutting down.
你的大脑缺氧 神经系统停止工作
So, by now, you can barely see me
所以现在你几乎看不到我
and now you can't hear me and now...
现在你还听不到我说话 而现在
...you're dead.
你死了
I'm just gonna go and have a word with your secretary.
我要和你的秘书说句话
Daniel Boyd, Senator Lavoy's legislative director.
丹尼尔博伊德 拉沃伊参议员的立法主任
Spoiled dipshit who's never lifted anything heavier
被宠坏的蠢货 一辈子从没举起过
than a Grey Goose bottle in his life.
任何比灰雁酒瓶更重的东西
C-plus student who got into UVA and Georgetown Law
以C+的成绩进入弗吉尼亚大学
thanks to Mommy and Daddy's connections. Real party boy.
和乔治敦法学院 这都多亏了他父母的关系
Two dismissed DWIs in college.
真正的派对男孩
Second year of law school, gets caught with a sex worker.
法学院第二年 他被抓到嫖娼
Charges mysteriously disappeared.
指控神秘消失
Took his 2.3 GPA straight into private practice.
平均成绩2.3 直接进入私人律所
And now he drafts legislation that decides the fate of the free world,
而现在他负责起草 决定我们命运的法案
telling his boss to vote on whatever benefits the lobbyists who wooed him best.
让他的老板给符合最会讨好他的 游说者的利益的内容投票
So, he was born somewhere between third and home base
所以他含着金钥匙出生
and never heard the word "consequence."
从没听说过“后果”这个词
You gonna pull a few moves from your sleazy-adjacent playbook?
你要用你那招 “比不道德差一点”的伎俩吗
That's the general idea.
我就是这么想的
Boyd's gonna be in Boston tonight for a fundraiser event at the Pops.
博伊德今晚将在波士顿 参加通俗乐团的筹款活动
We'll set him up like a bowling pin.
我们可以设个局 轻易拿捏他
Yeah. You pick up the phone.
- 怎么  - 你竟然接电话了
I thought maybe you couldn't answer because you broke your hand
我还以为你开车闯进那栋办公楼时
when you drove the fucking car through the office building.
弄伤了手 所以没法接呢
I didn't get hurt at all.
我根本没受伤
You think this is funny?
你觉得这很有趣吗
I told you no more cowboy shit.
我跟你说了 “别再搞牛仔那套”
The car belonged to one of their employees.
那辆车属于他们的一名员工
I was returning it.
我是去还车的
Listen, wiseass,
听我说 大聪明
my boss almost punched my ticket because of you.
我的老大因为你们差点把我开除了
Well, maybe that's a good thing
也许那是件好事
'cause members of my unit are falling from the sky like raindrops and you haven't done shit.
因为我小队的成员濒临死亡 而你什么都没做
Hey, hey. I want everything you got on New Age.
嘿 我想知道 你们从新时代得到的所有线索
- You understand? - Fine.
- 明白吗  - 好的
That's why I answered the phone this time. I actually have a reason to talk to you.
这就是我这次接电话的原因 我有理由跟你说话了
I'm gonna send you their security team roster.
我会把他们的安保团队名单发给你
Run background checks, see what connections these guys have.
查一下这些人有什么联系
W... Wait, wait, wait. What do you think-- I'm here to do your clerical work?
等等 怎么 你觉得 我是来给你们做文书工作的
Yup.
是啊
We're busy heading off to Boston.
我们正忙着去波士顿
What's in Boston?
波士顿有什么
The symphony.
交响乐
Goddamn it.
他妈的
Before we head north, though, Dixon and I should go talk to Marlo Burns,
但在我们去北边之前 迪克森和我应该去跟马洛伯恩斯谈谈
step on her neck a little bit.
给她施点压
Address is online.
网上有地址
Right there is why I don't have a house. Yeah, that's the reason.
- 这就是为何我不买房子 - 是啊 好借口
So, while we do all the work, what are you guys gonna do?
那么 我们干活的时候 你们要做什么
Oh, we're gonna go score some drugs.
我们要去拿些毒品
Howdy.
你们好啊
Oh, shit. Five-O! Five-O!
- 见鬼  - 警察
Well, that's just rude.
真没礼貌
This just ain't your week.
你这周运气不好
Find a new line of work, asshole.
混蛋 找份新工作吧
She's got a kid.
她有个孩子
House clear.
室内安全
Affirmative.
已确认
Anything interesting?
有什么有趣的发现吗
I mean, just some expensive jewelry Marlo left behind.
只有马洛留下的一些昂贵的珠宝
Left behind?
留下的
Think she bugged out?
你觉得她跑了
She exited out the back door without locking it,
她从后门出去了 门都没锁
clothes are all over, clearly packed in a hurry.
衣服扔得到处都是 显然是匆忙打包的
Closet and... cabinets are open.
衣橱和橱柜是开着的
Well, she took her toothbrush and toothpaste.
她拿走了牙刷和牙膏
Kidnappers don't care about oral hygiene.
绑匪通常不关心口腔卫生
Jane's a gamer.
简是个玩家
Got good taste.
品味不错
Uh, you might want to come and see this.
你可能想来看看这个
Who the hell goes on the lam and leaves their cash stash behind?
谁会逃跑的时候 不带上储备的现金啊
Apparently, Marlo Burns.
显然 马洛伯恩斯不会
So, to confirm, you've reserved a Cadillac Escalade,
确认一下 您预订了一辆凯迪拉克凯雷德
to be returned within three days' time to JFK Airport.
三天后返还到肯尼迪机场 对吗
That's correct.
没错
And to thank you for your loyalty,
为了答谢老顾客
we've upgraded you to a SiriusXM Platinum listening experience, free of charge.
我们免费给您升级到 SiriusXM白金聆听体验
Wonderful.
太棒了
Thank you for your business, Dr. Elzogby. Have a wonderful drive.
谢谢惠顾 埃尔佐格比医生 祝您旅途愉快
Would you like this?
你想要这个吗
Do you know why I love comic books so much?
你知道我为什么这么喜欢漫画书吗
Well, look at you.
看看你
Don't you feel more civilized now, Ms. Doolittle?
你不觉得现在更文明了吗 杜立特女士
Wait, where are the clothes you were wearing? Garbage.
- 你之前穿的那身衣服在哪里  - 垃圾桶
Garbage, why?
垃圾桶 为什么
I'm already carrying boots.
我已经提着靴子了
If I had any more clothes, pretty soon I'd need a suitcase.
如果我还有更多衣服的话 很快我就需要手提箱了
I got a suitcase, I need a house to keep it in.
要是我有了手提箱 我需要一个房子来存放它
Then I need a car for the driveway.
然后我还需要一辆车停在车道上
Before you know it, I'm filling out all kinds of forms.
很快 我就得填写各种表格
So, a spare shirt's just too much of an attachment for you?
所以 对你来说 一件备用衬衫太累赘了
Anyone ever diagnose you as a sociopath?
有人诊断说你是反社会人格吗
Diagnosed? No.
诊断 没有
So... what do you make of Marlo Burns taking off
那么 你觉得马洛伯恩斯 为什么慌忙逃跑
with just some clothes and leaving all that cash behind?
只带了几件衣服 把所有现金都留下
Not sure yet.
我还不确定
Well, she did take her toothbrush.
她确实拿走了牙刷
She could be your soul mate.
她应该是你的灵魂伴侣吧
Shut up.
闭嘴
Not one word.
一个字都别说
Holy shit. That's two words.
- 天啊 - 那是两个字了
Another one, and I'll shove this kitten heel right up your ass.
再说一个字 我就把这个小高跟插进你屁眼里
I'm just saying you look nice. You both look nice.
我只是说你很漂亮 你们俩都看起来不错
We look like the assholes on top of a wedding cake.
我们看起来就像婚礼蛋糕上的混蛋
Here, I'll pay you back in a month when my pension lands.
给 等我的养老金到账 我会在一个月内还给你的
Yeah, your pension won't cover that suit.
你的养老金可买不起那套西服
Or the hotel room. Or the plane ticket.
也付不起酒店房间 机票也付不起
I'll pay you back in two months.
我会在两个月内还清
Okay.
好的
Everyone ready?
大家都准备好了吗
Let's go listen to some boring-ass music.
我们去听无聊的音乐吧
Okay.
好的
And, uh, close your mouth, boss. You're catching flies.
闭上嘴巴 老大 你的嘴巴大得都快进苍蝇了
Excuse me.
借过
Thank you. Pardon me.
谢谢 对不起
- Excuse me. - Of course. Okay.
- 借过 - 没事
Oh, no, it's...
不对 这...
Apologies. Not at all.
- 抱歉 - 没事
I'm-I'm sorry. I'm a little turned around. I don't know if I have
对不起 我有点晕头转向的 我不知道我的座位
orchestra seats or floor box seats,
是在乐队席还是在楼层包厢
and I actually don't even know what that means.
我其实都不知道这是什么意思
- Okay, well... - Do you mind? Let's just see what we got here.
- 介意吗  - 我们看看票上写的什么
Hmm, the mezzanine, that's where you are, but... Okay.
- 夹层楼 那是你的位置... - 好的
that just simply won't cut it. You see, you want to be down here.
...但那座位可不怎么样 你会想坐在这里
The sound, it just wraps around you like a fleece.
声音就像羊毛一样包围着你
How about I swap your ticket with my aide when he arrives?
等我的助手来了 你跟他换个位置吧
Wouldn't he mind?
他不介意吗
Well, not if he wants to keep his job.
他要是想保住工作 就不会介意
Please, take a seat.
请坐吧
Thank you.
谢谢
In the bag.
稳操胜券
We go 13/14s. 8/13s.
我们有13/14 8/13
Over seven months, six-day working weeks.
总共七个月 每周工作六天
Maybe a time sheet clocking hours? Maybe a ratings scale? I don't know.
也许是一个记录时间的时间表  也许是一种评级标准 我不知道
Top you off?
需要加水吗
Yeah. Yes, ma'am.
- 需要 - 需要 女士
And when you get the chance, could you bring me the bill? This guy doesn't have any money.
还有 请把账单拿给我 好吗  这家伙没钱
Sure. Let me tally it up for you.
当然可以 让我帮你统计一下
Great.
太棒了
It's a tally.
这是统计
What?
什么
Here.
这里
13/14ths.
13/14
Something happened 13 times when it was supposed to happen 14 times.
某件事发生了13次 但本来应该发生14次
Uh, here, 11 out of 13. Eight out of 11.
这里 11次的13次 8次的11次
Hey, bud, I just...
嘿 伙计 我只是...
Okay, what did I tell you?
好的 我怎么跟你说的
Hands are for helping, not hitting.
手是用来帮忙的 不是用来打人的
Apologize to your brother. Share your Legos, okay?
向你的兄弟道歉 把你的乐高给他玩 好吗
I love you.
我爱你
To the moon and back.
我对你的爱可以往返月球
Okay, bye for now.
好的 再见了
Sorry, I don't know why I gave them my burner number, uh...
对不起 我不知道 我为什么要给他们我的一次性手机号
Well, you look happy.
你看起来很开心
I did the math.
我算了一下
There were 2,197 total events, whatever they were.
有2197个事件 不管具体是什么事
But they only succeeded 1,547 times. But that's not the interesting number.
但只成功了1547次 但这个数字并不有趣
Look how many times they didn't get the outcome they wanted.
看看他们有多少次 没得到他们想要的结果
2,197 minus 1,547.
2197减去1547
Six hundred and fifty. Holy shit.
650天啊
Six fifty at 100K each.
六千五 每手十万
It's all connected somehow.
这一切都以某种方式联系在一起
So...
那么...
So... hands are for helping?
那么 “手是用来帮忙的”
You have brass knuckles in your pocket.
你口袋里还装着铜指虎
I got a PAW Patrol Band-Aid and some playground sand, too.
我有《狗狗巡逻队》的创可贴 还有操场的沙子
Look, they call nonstop when I'm not there.
听着 我不在的时候 他们不停地打电话 我...
And when I am there, it's, you know,
我在家的时候
7:00 a.m. weekend soccer games,
要早上7点去周末足球比赛
teacher conferences,
参加教师会议
scheduled sex with the wife.
与妻子预订的做爱
I am no longer my own man.
我不再孑然一身
And you wouldn't trade it for anything in the world.
你不会拿它换世界上任何东西
Not for $65 million.
六千五百万美元都不行
You are a changed man, O'Donnell.
你彻底变了 奥唐纳
Yep. Maybe you should give it a go, huh?
是啊 也许你应该试试
Buy some land, start a family.
买些土地 组建个家庭
You'd be the scariest guy at PTA, but you'd be a good dad.
你会是亲师会上最可怕的人 但你会是个好爸爸
- If I had land, I'd get four or five... - Four or five dogs.
- 要是我有土地 我会有四... - 四五条狗
You'd get four or five dogs, no woman?
你会有四五条狗 没有女人
Not even Dixon?
连迪克森都不要
She's a friend.
她是朋友
Okay.
好吧
Whatever you say. That was some dress, though.
随你怎么说吧 就像是一件衣服
Hell of a dress.
是一件很好的衣服
From Neagley. It's intermission.
是内格利的消息 现在是中场休息
Dixon and Boyd are leaving now.
迪克森和博伊德现在要走了
There they are.
他们在那里
That's one hell of a dress.
真是一件很好的衣服啊
My car's around the corner. Does that work?
我的车在拐角处 那样可以吗
I'll follow anywhere you lead, gorgeous.
我会跟着你走 美女
- Well, let's go party. - Okay.
- 我们去派对吧 - 好的
Look at her.
看看她
Boyd didn't stand a chance.
博伊德没机会
Neagley again. She says my guy's in place.
又是内格利 她说我的人就位了
Hey, this friend of yours. He's gonna come through for us, yeah?
嘿 你的这位朋友会帮我们 对吧
If he was in the Army, I'd have asked him to join the 110th.
如果他在军队的话 我会邀请他加入110小组
Come here.
过来
Oh, you're all riled up.
你都兴奋了
Well, what can I say? Classical music gets my motor running.
我能说什么 古典音乐让我兴奋
Yeah, well, drop it to second, Speed Racer. Let's have a little primer first.
慢一点 极速赛车手 我们先来点前戏
You're not messing around. All right.
你不是在胡闹 好吧
- There we go. Ooh. Ooh. - Yeah. Yes.
- 好啦 好的 拿着这个 - 是的
Okay, hold this. Hold... hold that.
拿着
I never know how thick or thin to make these things.
我一直不知道要弄多厚或者多薄...
Hey, allow me.
嘿 我来吧
Thank you.
谢谢
Okay. Ladies first?
好了 女士优先
Oh, no, you did the work, you get the reward.
不 你弄的 你应该得到奖励
If you insist.
恭敬不如从命
Shit. Shit. Just-just play it cool, just play it cool. Just play it cool.
糟了 努力保持冷静
Sir, you're gonna want to put the drugs away and step out of the car.
先生 你得把毒品收起来 然后下车
They're not my drugs.
那不是我的毒品
Which drugs--
哪些毒品
the ones on your mirror or up your nose?
你化妆镜里的 还是你鼻子上的
You think I own a makeup mirror? They're all hers.
你觉得化妆镜是我的吗  全都是她的
Not what she's saying, and she wasn't holding it.
跟她说的不一样 而且她又没拿化妆镜
And she already offered up blood and urine.
她已经提出进行血检和尿检
Do you want to offer up blood and urine?
你想进行血检和尿检吗
Listen, Officer,
听我说 长官
I hate putting it this way, but... do you know who I am?
我不愿意这么说 但你知道我是谁吗
I do, actually, Mr. Boyd.
我其实知道 博伊德先生
And I know that woman in the car wasn't Mrs. Boyd.
我还知道车里的那个女人 不是博伊德太太
And I have a special distaste for people
我特别讨厌那些
who don't appreciate the sanctity of marriage.
不珍惜神圣的婚姻的人
I also know you work for Senator Lavoy.
我也知道你是拉沃伊参议员的手下
But when I ran your name in the system,
但我在系统里查你的名字时
it set off bells and whistles at the local FBI office.
触发了当地联邦调查局的警报
They sent a couple of their boys down here just to talk to you.
他们派了几个人过来跟你聊聊
And it seems they don't care who your boss is.
他们似乎并不在乎你的老板是谁
Special Agent Jack Margrave.
我是杰克马格雷福特工
This is Special Agent Blake.
这是布雷克特工
Lieutenant Oscar Finlay.
我是奥斯卡芬雷中尉
Yeah, I'm not talking without my lawyer.
律师不在场 我不会说话
You want to lawyer up?
你想请律师吗
Fine. Call them.
好的 给他打电话吧
I will. And they'll have me out of here within the hour.
我会的 他们一小时内 就会把我弄出去
You know...
你知道
...that's just gonna be too late.
那就太晚了
Because by the time they get here,
因为等他们到这里时
we'll already have the story of a senator's legislative director
我们就已经 在《环球报》和《先驱报》的头版
in the wrong woman's car with a snout full of booger sugar
刊登了一位参议员的立法主任
on the front page of the Globe and the Herald.
坐在错误的女人的车里 鼻子里全是可卡因的报道
You see,
你知道
this is not college or law school, son.
这不是大学或法学院 孩子
You're not some spoiled rich kid barely rocking a C-plus.
你也不是被宠坏的 勉强拿到C+的富家子弟
You're a Beltway man now.
你现在是个政客
Kind of guy that people enjoy knocking down a peg or two.
是人们喜欢搞垮的那种人
So these charges,
所以这些指控
they're not just gonna get swept under the rug.
它们可不会逃过大众的法眼
We're not gonna let 'em.
我们不会让他们这样
Want to know why?
想知道原因吗
Okay. Why?
好吧 为什么
'Cause we don't like you.
因为我们不喜欢你
I don't even know why you're here.
我甚至都不知道你们为什么来这里
We're here 'cause we want to know everything there is to know
我们在这里是因为 我们想知道关于小翅膀计划的
about Little Wing.
所有信息
- I should probably... - Yeah, you should.
- 我也许应该... - 你应该
Yeah. I'm gonna call Mr. Boyd's wife.
是啊 我要给 博伊德先生的妻子打电话
Eh, she's probably worried about him over in D.C.
她可能在华盛顿担心他
Worried sick.
非常担心
You know, happy wife, happy life, huh?
老婆开心 生活舒心
Okay. Fine.
好吧
- Hello? - Wrong number.
- 你好  - 我打错了
Talk.
说话
It's not that big of a deal.
这没什么大不了的
Little Wing is just a code name.
小翅膀只是个代号
For what?
什么的代号
For a new technology currently in development.
一项目前正在开发的新技术的代号
Some incredible anti-missile software
一个令人难以置信的反导弹软件
originally developed to protect commercial aircraft,
它最初是为保护商用飞机而开发的
but a certain aeronautics company approached us.
但某个航空公司找到了我们
Let me guess--
让我猜猜
New Age?
新时代
That's right. New Age.
是的 新时代
They found the software could be tweaked.
他们发现该软件可以做些调整
It could be used in missiles and not just against them.
它可以用于导弹中 而且不仅仅是针对它们
It could be scaled down
它还可以缩小
and installed in portable shoulder-fired surface-to-air weaponry.
安装在便携式肩扛式地对空武器中
The software allows missiles to defeat
这个软件能让导弹击破
all known countermeasures. How?
- 所有已知的对抗措施 - 怎么做到的
That's a question for a nerd in a lab coat, man.
那是穿着实验室制服的 书呆子才会问的问题
Okay? All I know is
好吧 我只知道
that missiles shot from the ground completely bypass their target,
从地面发射的导弹 能完全绕过它们的目标
making pilots believe the threat has passed,
让飞行员相信威胁已经过去
and then they recalibrate, turn around,
然后它们重新校准 转身
zero back in on the aircraft and reattack.
重新瞄准飞机 重新进行攻击
It's death from above and there is no way to avoid it.
这必死无疑 无法避免
You fire, you hit your target. Period.
你开火 就能射中目标 就是这样
And what's Senator Lavoy's involvement?
那拉沃伊参议员参与了什么
Well, the project required an appropriation bill, all right?
项目需要一个拨款法案 好吗
You want to get one passed?
你想要通过一个法案
You're looking at years of bureaucratic bullshit
就得面对多年的繁文缛节
all thanks to some arcane laws on modifying civilian tech.
这都要归功于一些 关于修改民用技术的古怪法律
But Lavoy knew Little Wing would slingshot our military into the future,
但拉沃伊知道小翅膀 会带领我们的军队走向未来
so if we just sat on our hands,
所以如果我们袖手旁观
waiting for it to go through the proper channels,
等待申请通过正规渠道
it would never happen.
那永远都无法落实
So I'm assuming Lavoy didn't clear up the red tape
所以我猜拉沃伊没有以最体面的方式
in the most reputable manner?
清除繁文缛节
I helped bury the proposal in a thousand-page statute
我帮忙把提案塞进了 一份一千页的法规中
while Lavoy shook hands and drummed up votes.
与此同时 拉沃伊负责握手拉选票
No one even knew it was in there.
甚至都没人知道法案里有这个
And he did this out of the goodness of his heart?
他纯粹是好心做这事
To protect democracy?
为了保护民主
No fat envelopes slipped inside newspapers on park benches?
没有收红包之类的
Grow the fuck up, okay?
成熟点 好吗
It's D.C. It's how shit gets done.
这是华盛顿特区 这是办事的规矩
Besides, Lavoy knew Little Wing would save lives.
此外 拉沃伊知道小翅膀会拯救生命
I mean...
我的意思是
everyone made fun of the Star Wars defense program,
每个人都嘲笑星球大战的防御计划
but, hey, look at where we are now.
但看看我们现在的处境
Everyone's trying to shoot projectiles out of the air.
每个人都想从空中发射炮弹
Little Wing can knock anything out of the sky.
小翅膀可以击中空中的任何物体
Anything?
任何物体
Like commercial aircraft?
比如商用飞机
You fire, you hit the target.
你开火 就能击中目标
You said so yourself. Yeah, but it's our tech. We have it.
- 你自己说的 - 对 但这是我们的技术 归我们所有
Nobody else can get their hands on it.
其他人都无法得到它
Nothing like you're thinking is going to happen.
你们想的那种事是不会发生的
New Age is incredibly secure. Both of their facilities
新时代非常安全 他们的两个场所都采用了
- implement state-of-the-art... - Both facilities?
- 最先进的... - 两个场所
What do you mean?
什么意思
New Age has two bases.
新时代有两个基地
Software made in New York,
软件是在纽约开发的
hardware at a manufacturing plant in Denver.
硬件是在丹佛的制造工厂制造的
What else can you tell us?
还有什么
Nothing. That's all I know. I swear.
没了 我发誓我就知道这些
Hey, Lavoy and me-- we-we cut some corners,
嘿 拉沃伊和我 我们走了捷径
we did some stuff we should not have done,
我们确实做了一些不该做的事
but it was all to get a defense bill passed,
但这都是为了让国防法案通过
protect the country.
保护国家
How'd that work out?
那结果如何
Hey, excuse me. So, are the drug charges getting dropped or what?
嘿 抱歉 所以毒品指控会被撤销吗
I don't know. I'm not a cop.
我不知道 我不是警察
Heck of a surprise getting a call from you.
真意外 居然接到你的电话
Hell of a surprise hearing you're wearing the badge again.
听说你又戴上警徽了 真是太意外了
Lieutenant, no less.
中尉 彼此彼此
Yeah, well, retirement didn't suit me.
是啊 退休可不适合我
Speaking of suits, see you're still sporting the tweed.
说起来 我看你还穿着呢子大衣
Reliable as ever, Finlay.
一如既往的可靠 芬雷
Speak for yourself.
你是说你自己吧
What was it you told me when we first met--
我们初次见面时 你跟我说了什么
trouble always seems to find you?
“麻烦似乎总是找上你”
You kill a whole lot of people?
你杀了很多人吗
Here and there. You need my help?
- 时不时 - 需要帮忙吗
Already gave it.
你已经帮我了
You still spinning that wedding ring?
你还在转那枚结婚戒指吗
Here and there. But feeling better every day.
时不时 但感觉一天比一天好
- And the dog? - Jack eats too much.
- 狗呢  - 杰克很能吃
Just like his namesake.
狗如其名
Today, boss. Car's running, and if I don't get out of this straitjacket soon,
今天 老大 汽车正在行驶 如果我不尽快脱掉这件紧身衣
things are gonna get ugly. Neagley?
- 事情会变得很难看的 - 内格利
Didn't recognize you. Looking good.
我都没认出你 看起来很美
Mind your business, elbow patches.
别多管闲事 补丁男
Hey, you heard the lady.
你听到这位女士说的了
If I don't have her in jeans in 20 minutes,
如果我20分钟内不让她穿上牛仔裤
I'm done for.
我就完蛋了
See you around, Reacher.
回见 雷彻
See you around, Finlay.
回见 芬雷
So, Little Wing could be our next 9/11.
所以小翅膀可能会铸就下一起911
What are our directives?
我们的指令是什么
You and Dixon go to Denver.
你和迪克森去丹佛
The Little Wing software is useless without the missile hardware,
小翅膀软件需要导弹硬件
and that's where it's made.
那是硬件的制造地
Maybe you can gum up the works, keep the missiles out of the wrong hands.
也许你们可以干扰一下 以免导弹落入坏人之手
O'Donnell and I will head down to D.C.
奥唐纳和我会去华盛顿特区
Want to swing by Homeland, see what they know about A.M.
我想去国土安全局 看看他们是否知道AM的事
If taking out airplanes is his M.O., they might have some intel on him.
如果他的作案手法是将人扔出飞机 他们可能有些情报
How do you figure we're gonna do that?
我们要怎么做
You think we're just gonna knock on the door and say, "Can the DoD come out and play?"
你觉得我们就直接敲门说 “国防部能出来玩吗 ”
My brother worked for Homeland.
我兄弟在国土安全局工作
His contacts can help us.
他的联系人能帮到我们
Oh, no shit. How's Joe doing these days?
对哦 乔最近过得怎么样
He's dead.
他死了
I'm starving. We should eat.
我饿了 我们应该吃饭
Dibs on the bathroom. I need to get changed.
我有权用浴室 我得换衣服
Yeah? You gonna throw it in the garbage like our sociopathic friend here?
是吗 你要把这衣服扔进垃圾桶 就像这位反社会朋友一样吗
Oh, why, you want to borrow it?
不会 怎么 你想借
Oh, yeah. I got the ass for it.
是啊 我很喜欢
Hate to ruin prom night,
我很讨厌破坏舞会之夜
but hand over your guns.
但交出你们的枪
What makes you think we have guns?
你为什么觉得我们有枪
We were told you'd be packing, Reacher.
有人跟我们说你们有枪 雷彻
They also tell you you'd die tonight?
他们还跟你说 今晚你会死吗
I'll die? That's funny.
我会死 真搞笑
No guns, so no noise.
没有枪 所以没有噪音
They said you were smart.
他们说你们很聪明
I'm gonna cut you,
我要砍死你
gut you
割了你
and leave you...
让你...
Everyone okay?
大家都还好吗
Yeah. It'll heal.
还好 会愈合的
Never better.
不能更好了
Fucked up my shoes,
我的鞋坏了
but I'm fine.
但我没事
Yeah.
嗯
Before you ask if it's done, it is,
不用你问出口 已经完事了
just not in the way you hoped for.
只是跟你希望的方式不同
You're causing a very complex operation a lot of problems.
你造成了很多复杂的问题
Sixty-five million dollars worth, Langston?
价值六千五百万美元 兰斯顿
Assume that's who I'm talking to.
我猜你就是兰斯顿吧
Head of security?
安保部老大
Head of this whole thing?
整件事的老大
Maybe we've been approaching this the wrong way, Mr. Reacher.
也许我们一直在用 错误的方式处理此事 雷彻先生
Just Reacher.
叫我雷彻
Okay, Reacher. Why don't we make a deal?
好吧 雷彻 不如我们做笔交易吧
I have the means to give you anything you could ask for.
你想要什么我都能给你
What is it that you want?
你想要什么
I want to throw you out of a helicopter.
我想把你扔出直升机